educationpost.org 2017-11-19

# Terms of Use and Privacy Policy - Education Post

#### Privacy and Terms of Use

Education Post values the privacy of individuals who visit our web site. This statement sets forth the important information which you need to know about how we collect and use personal information from web site visitors.

#### Collection of Information

The type and amount of information we receive about you depends entirely on how you use our site. For instance, you may read and download information provided on the site without providing any personal information at all. Our web server will collect your domain name (for example, [www.aol.com](http://www.aol.com/)) and means of entry to our web site (for example, via a particular search engine), the date, time and duration of each visit and the site pages visited. This information is collected and used for informational purposes only. We use this information to measure site usage and to make the site more beneficial to our visitors.

Personal information including name, location, e-mail address, company affiliation, telephone number, etc. is provided on a voluntary basis only. We use this information to respond to inquiries and requests for further information. We will not share or sell the personal information you provide us to a third party at any time. Education Post takes reasonable precautions to keep all information obtained from our online visitors secure against unauthorized access.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that web sites commonly write to the site visitor’s hard drive when a site is visited. A cookie file contains information that can identify a return visitor each time he or she visits our site. The data is encrypted for added security. Our web site may use cookies as a way to measure activity and traffic patterns on the site in order to continually improve the visitor’s experience. Cookies also provide visitors the convenience of not having to log in a password more than once our site, thereby saving the visitor time while on our site.

A browser can be set to warn the users before accepting cookies. Users can choose to refuse cookies by turning them off in the browser. Users do not need to have cookies turned on to visit our web site, but will need them to use certain customizable features on the site that we may launch in the future.

#### Children and Privacy

Education Post does not knowingly collect information from or about children age 13 and under.

#### External Links

Our site contains links to other Internet web sites, and Education Post is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any linked sites.

#### Changes to Policy

If Education Post decides to change its privacy policies and practices, we will post those changes to our Privacy Policy on our web site in advance of the changes taking effect, so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will continue to be able to use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.

#### Disclaimer

All of the information on this web site is presented in good faith and believed to be correct. However, Education Post makes no representations or warranties as to the completeness or accuracy of this information.

Information is supplied upon the condition that persons receiving it will make their own determination as to its suitability for their use. In no event will Education Post be responsible for damages of any nature whatsoever resulting from the use of or reliance upon this information.

No representations or warranties, either express or implied, of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose or of any other nature are made hereunder with respect to information or the product to which information refers.

#### Unsubscribe

To unsubscribe from any Education Post electronic newsletter, please send an email request to [info@educationpost.org](mailto:info@educationpost.org) and type the word “unsubcribe” in the subject line.

#### Questions

Any questions regarding this statement should be directed to our site coordinator at [info@educationpost.org](mailto:info@educationpost.org).
